<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019 Dylan Coakley <info@photoflare.io> -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.photoflare.photoflare</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>PhotoFlare</name>
  <summary>Simple but powerful Cross Platform Image Editor</summary>

  <description>
    <p>
      This is an effort to bring quick, simple but powerful image editing to the masses. PhotoFlare is inspired by the image editor currently only available on Microsoft Windows – PhotoFiltre. However, it will not be a straight clone. It is being built from the ground up to be much improved and cross platform too!
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Easy quick cropping tool.</li>
      <li>Flip, Rotate and scale images.</li>
      <li>Lots of unique image filters.</li>
      <li>Batch processing tool with support for all editor features.</li>
      <li>Multiple translations are supported.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.photoflare.photoflare.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Main Window</caption>
      <image>http://photoflare.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/CrossPlatform.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">http://photoflare.io</url>
  <project_group>PhotoFlare</project_group>

  <provides>
    <binary>photoflare</binary>
  </provides>

  <releases>
  <release version="1.5.8" date="2019-03-10">
      <description>
 		<ul>
			<li>Fixed selection changes adding an undo step when it should not.</li>
			<li>Fixed restart app button not working after language change.</li>
			<li>Fixed upper case file extensions not being opened correctly.</li>
			<li>Fixed allowing zero values on image resize in Batch/Automate.</li>
			<li>Fixed cancel on Image Size setting incorrect image dimensions in status area.</li>
			<li>Fixed being able to toggle show grid without an image.</li>
			<li>Fixed cancel on show grid still marking menuItem as checked.</li>
			<li>Fixed dialogs not being a window type of application modal.</li>
			<li>Fixed being able to uncheck direction on Gradient Dialog.</li>
			<li>Fixed maintaining image ratio for Resize dialog.</li>
			<li>Fixed Window Title typo on Transparent colour Dialog.</li>
		</ul>
      </description>
  </release>
  <release version="1.5.7" date="2019-02-18">
      <description>
 		<ul>
			<li>Fixed user only able to set Pixels as default unit via preferences.</li>
			<li>Fixed copy not taking selected area instead of full image.</li>
			<li>Fixed scaled corners not being clickable.</li>
			<li>Fixed imageRatio not being set correctly.</li>
			<li>Fixed gamma data type for batch processing.</li>
			<li>Added full Czech (CZ) translation.</li>
			<li>Added feature to detect and change invalid file extensions.</li>
			<li>Improved layout of gradient dialog.</li>
			<li>Improved selection lines to depend on scale.</li>
		</ul>
      </description>
  </release>
  </releases>
</component>
