<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2021 Dylan Coakley <info@photoflare.io> -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.photoflare.photoflare</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Photoflare</name>
  <summary>Simple but powerful Cross Platform Image Editor</summary>

  <description>
    <p>
      This is an effort to bring quick, simple but powerful image editing to the masses. PhotoFlare is inspired by the image editor currently only available on Microsoft Windows – PhotoFiltre. However, it will not be a straight clone. It is being built from the ground up to be much improved and cross platform too!
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Easy quick cropping tool.</li>
      <li>Flip, Rotate and scale images.</li>
      <li>Lots of unique image filters.</li>
      <li>Batch processing tool with support for all editor features.</li>
      <li>Multiple translations are supported.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">photoflare.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Main Window</caption>
      <image>http://photoflare.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/CrossPlatform.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://photoflare.io</url>
  <project_group>Photoflare</project_group>

  <provides>
    <binary>photoflare</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="1.6.8" date="2021-05-05">
        <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Fixed stripes appearing in filters that use openMP on Windows.</li>
          </ul>
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.6.7.1" date="2021-03-25">
        <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Fixed Paint Bucket tool not selecting colour from correct cursor position.</li>
            <li>Fixed Colour Picker tool not selecting colour from correct cursor position.</li>
            <li>Fixed the prepare file type code causing issues opening files.</li>
            <li>Added FileType detected to the Image Properties dialog.</li>
            <li>Added Spanish and Indonesian translations.</li>
            <li>Fixed Russian translation missing files from Windows portable version.</li>
          </ul>
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.6.6" date="2020-11-14">
        <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Fixed warning dialog showing on uppercase image formats.</li>
            <li>Fixed selecting Batch filters with no filter selected causes a crash.</li>
            <li>Fixed Eraser Tool setting should not be called Radius.</li>
            <li>Fixed Eraser Tool not making use of your secondary colour.</li>
            <li>Fixed issue with semi opaque images and filters.</li>
            <li>Fixed crash if restarting the app via Preferences dialog and files are still open.</li>
            <li>Fixed Undo history not being cleared after closing a file.</li>
            <li>Fixed SprayCan Tool allowing 1 pixel as radius value.</li>
            <li>Fixed Smudge Tool allowing 1 pixel as radius value.</li>
            <li>Fixed file preview limits too small on NewDialog.</li>
            <li>Fixed text size of zero being allowed in the TextDialog.</li>
            <li>Fixed crash when using color threshold filter on smaller images.</li>
            <li>Fixed crash when closing the TransparentDialog.</li>
            <li>Russian comment and Generic name added to Desktop file.</li>
            <li>Fixed loading of local translation files.</li>
            <li>Fixed flood fill not working with transparent image formats.</li>
            <li>Full Russian translation.</li>
          </ul>
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.6.5" date="2020-06-01">
        <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Fixed crash with colour picker.</li>
            <li>Full Swedish translation.</li>
          </ul>
        </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
