<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2021 Dylan Coakley <info@photoflare.io> -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.photoflare.photoflare</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Photoflare</name>
  <summary>Simple but powerful Cross Platform Image Editor</summary>

  <description>
    <p>
      This is an effort to bring quick, simple but powerful image editing to the masses. PhotoFlare is inspired by the image editor currently only available on Microsoft Windows – PhotoFiltre. However, it will not be a straight clone. It is being built from the ground up to be much improved and cross platform too!
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Easy quick cropping tool.</li>
      <li>Flip, Rotate and scale images.</li>
      <li>Lots of unique image filters.</li>
      <li>Batch processing tool with support for all editor features.</li>
      <li>Multiple translations are supported.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">photoflare.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Main Window</caption>
      <image>http://photoflare.io/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/CrossPlatform.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://photoflare.io</url>
  <project_group>Photoflare</project_group>

  <provides>
    <binary>photoflare</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="1.6.10" date="2022-05-08">
        <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Added fine grained image rotation.</li>
            <li>Added unlock ratio feature to resize canvas.</li>
            <li>Fixed drawing performance regression caused by canvas shadow effect.</li>
            <li>Fixed missing taskbar icon on KDE plasma by @saikat0511.</li>
            <li>Updated Dutch translation by @Vistaus.</li>
          </ul>
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.6.9" date="2021-06-26">
        <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Fixed TextDialog colour widget missing border around selected colour.</li>
            <li>Fixed being able to select a colour outside image bounds.</li>
            <li>Fixed show selection not enabled after dragging new selection area.</li>
            <li>Fixed the canvas area blending into MdiArea if same bg colour used.</li>
            <li>Fixed hiding the toolpalette should also hide the brush options.</li>
            <li>Fixed incomplete batch summary information.</li>
            <li>Fixed batch rotation incorrectly triggered.</li>
            <li>Fixed QMetaObject runtime messages being output to terminal.</li>
          </ul>
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.6.8" date="2021-05-05">
        <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Fixed stripes appearing in filters that use openMP on Windows.</li>
          </ul>
        </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.6.7.1" date="2021-03-25">
        <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Fixed Paint Bucket tool not selecting colour from correct cursor position.</li>
            <li>Fixed Colour Picker tool not selecting colour from correct cursor position.</li>
            <li>Fixed the prepare file type code causing issues opening files.</li>
            <li>Added FileType detected to the Image Properties dialog.</li>
            <li>Added Spanish and Indonesian translations.</li>
            <li>Fixed Russian translation missing files from Windows portable version.</li>
          </ul>
        </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
